Hi, and welcome to session 20,
嗨，欢迎来到第 20 节课，
in this session, we're gonna talk about all the chords you ever needed to know,
在这节课中，我们将讨论所有你需要知道的和弦，
we've gone over quite a few chords up at this point,
我们现在已经学习了相当多的和弦，
but now we're just gonna cover a couple of little gaps that we haven't been able to hit yet.
但现在我们只需要弥补几个我们还没有达到的小差距。
So in this session, we're gonna learn about chords and inversions,
在这节课中，我们将学习和弦和转位，
chords and there are abbreviations which we haven't gotten into yet,
和弦，还有一些缩写，我们还没有学到，
gonna learn about alternate bass chords,
学习其他低音和弦，
like a D with an F# in the bass,
比如 D 和 F# 的低音和弦，
we're gonna learn some very cool open sounded E-B kind of drone chord,
我们将学习一些非常酷的开放式 E-B drone 和弦，
as soon as I play them, you'll recognize them,
我一弹出来，你就会认出它们，
we'll learn about diminished chords, augmented chords,
我们将学习减弱和弦，增强和弦，
they'll give you forms and all of those,
它们会给你形式和所有这些，
as well as building unfamiliar chords,
以及建立不熟悉的和弦，
if you don't know what a chord is,
如果你不知道和弦是什么，
we'll teach you how to build it,
我们可以教你如何制作它，
and resources where you can find out new information on chord forms.
在那里你可以找到关于和弦形式的新信息。
In the guitar tips section,
在吉他技巧部分，
we're going to cover practicing, how to effectively practice,
我们将包括练习，如何有效地练习，
the power of warming up,
热身的力量，
and the key to playing fast,
弹奏快的关键，
the power of inspiration and perseverance and the keys to being a good musician.
灵感和毅力的力量，以及成为一名优秀音乐家的关键。
So we've got a lot to cover,
我们有很多内容要讲，
so let's go ahead and get started.
所以让我们继续并开始吧。
Okay, so let's start talking about chords,
好的，让我们开始讨论和弦，
and now we've learned a good bit about chords,
现在我们对和弦有了很好的了解，
and here's the last little gasp of chords, that we need to learn,
这是我们需要学习的最后一小段和弦，
before I set you off and let you loosen the real world.
在我开始让你们放松现实世界之前。
Okay, we've covered barre chords,
好的，我们已经讲过的横按和弦，
are Fs, C#m, C#m7,
有 F C#m C#m7 ，
five string, six string barre chords,
五弦，六弦横按和弦，
we've covered major sevens, minor sevens,
我们介绍了大七和弦，小七和弦，
we've covered ninth chords,
我们介绍了九和弦，
a little bit about thirteenth chords as well.
还有一点关于十三和弦。
Okay, now we're gonna look at a couple of more things about those chords,
好的，现在我们来看看更多关于和弦的东西，
now remember, a C major triad has the notes C E and G in it,
记得 C 大调三和弦中有 C E G 音符，
a major triad, there's nothing by the chord.
一个大调三和弦，和弦上什么都没有，
Let's talk about some abbreviations,
让我们来谈谈一些缩略语，
if you don't see anything by a chord,
如果你看不到和弦上任何东西，
you just see a C, an F or a G,
你只看到 C F 或 G ，
that's a major triad and you're dealing with there,
这是一个大调的三和弦，你在那里处理，
if it's a C, it'd be a C E G,
如果是 C ，就是 C E G ，
F, F A C,
如果是 F ，就是 F A C ，
now, if you're dealing with a minor chord in triads,
现在，如果你在处理小三和弦，
well, some of the abbreviations you might see would be,
你可能会看到一些缩写，
like a C with an m [], that would be minor,
比如 C 加上 m ，就是小调，
or Cmin,
或者 Cmin ，
or maybe even a C with a minus sign,
或者甚至是 C 加上减号，
that's kind of a Jazz way of writing it.
这是一种爵士乐的写法。
Okay, augmented chords,
好的，增强和弦，
sometimes you'll see Caug, aug the abbreviation for that,
有时你会看到 Caug ，这是它的缩写，
sometimes you'll see just a plus sign,
有时你只会看到一个加号，
the plus sign is telling you that that is an augmented chord.
加号告诉你这是一个增强和弦。
Okay, now let's talk about diminished, diminished triads,
好的，现在让我们来谈谈减三和弦，
if I see a little zero up at the top of the chord,
如果我看到一个小零在和弦上面，
kind of a superscript zero up there,
就像有一个上标零，
that's a diminished,
那就是一个减弱，
that's what they're trying to tell you,
这就是他们想要告诉你的，
sometimes you'll see it a Cdim,
有时你会看到 Cdim ，
but most often you'll see it with the little zero up at the top.
但大多数情况下，你会看到上面有一个小零。
Okay, now when we get into seventh chord,
好的，当我们进入第七和弦时，
these abbreviations get a little bit trickier,
这些缩略语就变得有点棘手了，
okay, a major seventh can be written Cmaj7,
好的，大七和弦可以写为 Cmaj7 ，
or it can be written with a C with a triangle seventh,
也可以写作 C 和三角形 7 ，
that triangle seventh is telling you,
那个三角形 7 是在告诉你，
that's you're dealing with a major seventh,
你面对的是一个大七，
even if it's a Cmaj9 or Cmaj13 or whatever,
即使它是 Cmaj9 或 Cmaj13 或其他什么，
if it has that triangle in there,
如果里面有那个三角形，
that's equivalent to the word major.
就相当于大调这个词。
Okay, minor seventh,
好的，小七和弦，
it would be C minor seventh or Cmin7
C 小七和弦是 Cmin7
or Cm7 or even C-7,
或 Cm7 或 C-7 ，
common abbreviations form.
常见的缩略形式。
For a dominant seventh chord,
对于属七和弦，
that would be just a letter name and seven,
它只是一个字母和 7 ，
F7 G7 A7.
F7 G7 A7 。
Okay, for a half diminished,
好的，对于半减和弦，
it would be a circle with a slash through it,
它将是一个圆圈，上面有一个斜线，
okay, if diminished is a circle,
好的，如果减弱是一个圆圈，
then half diminished would be a circle with a slash through it.
那么半减就是一个带斜线的圆圈。
Okay, with ninth, eleventh and thirteenth,
好的，对于第九、第十一和第十三，
you just add whatever number of notes that you need to to get up to that chord.
你只需添加任何数的音符，就可以达到那个和弦。
Let's do some examples,
让我们举几个例子，
what would a C7,
C7 是什么，
and then look, I've got some parentheses there and a b9,
看，我在那里有一个圆括号和一个 b9 ，
so what is that telling you,
那么这告诉了你什么，
well, that's telling you,
这是在告诉你，
that's a C7 chord, C E G Bb,
那是 C7 和弦， C E G Bb ，
and they want the ninth in there,
他们想要第九个在那里，
but they want it flatted,
但他们想要降调的，
which would be A Db,
这将是 Db ，
that chord would be something like this,
这个和弦应该是这样的，
you can also do C7 #9, like that.
你也可以做 C7(#9) ，就像这样。
What about that other one I have done there,
那我在那里做的另一个呢，
I was just kind of having some fun,
我只是在找点意思，
an F-11 with a b5 b9,
F-11 加上 b5 b9 ，
oh my goodness, what is that,
我的天哪，这是什么，
no problem, you just figure it out one step at a time,
没问题，你只需要一步一步地弄清楚，
F-, so it's F Ab C,
F- ，所以它是 F Ab C ，
it doesn't say major seven,
它没有说大调 7 ，
so it's an Eb in there,
所以它是 Eb 在这里，
so what do we have,
那么我们有什么，
F Ab C Eb and then G and then Bb,
F Ab C Eb G Bb ，
okay, that's the eleventh,
好的，那是第十一，
but look what we have to do,
但看看我们要做什么，
we have to flat that fifth,
我们要对 5 降调，
so instead of the C, it becomes a Cb,
所以它不是 C ，而是 Cb ，
instead of the G, it becomes a Gb,
不是 G ，它变成了 Gb ，
so the whole chord written out would be an F Ab Cb Eb Gb and a Bb.
所以写出的整个和弦是 F Ab Cb Eb Gb Bb 。
Okay, that's a little bit about abbreviations.
好的，这是关于缩写的一点。
Let's talk about inversions,
让我们来谈谈转位，
this is something you'll see quite often,
这是你会经常看到的，
slash is, you have, you'll have a note and then you'll have a slash and then you'll have another note,
你会有一个音符，然后你会有一个斜杠，然后你会有另一个音符，
well, what in the world are they talking about there,
那么，他们在那里到底在谈论什么呢，
the note that is underneath the slash is the note that's in the bass,
斜杠下面的音符是低音的音符，
okay, so in our first example there,
好的，在我们的第一个例子中，
it's a G/B,
它是 G/B ，
so that's telling you,
所以这告诉你，
they want a G chord, but they want the B as the lowest note,
他们想要 G 和弦，但他们想要 B 作为最低的音符，
okay, so instead of playing a G chord like this,
好的，不是像这样弹奏 G 和弦，
I'd have to play the B is the lowest note
我来弹奏 B 是最低的音符，
and that would be a G with a B in the bass,
这是 G ，使用 B 作为低音，
or you could do it like this.
或者你可以这样做。
Okay, next one would be like a D with an F# in the bass,
好的，下一个是 D 使用 F# 作为低音，
very common chord,
很常见的和弦，
it's a D chord, F# is the lowest pitch,
它是 D 和弦， F# 是最低音，
so you'd have to put the F# in the bottom,
所以你必须把 F# 放在底部，
and a common way to do that is something like this.
通常的方法是这样做。
So G with a B in the bass,
所以， G 使用 B 作为低音，
D with an F# in the bass,
D 使用 F# 作为低音，
would be something like that.
应该是这样的。
Now, sometimes the bass note is not necessarily part of the chord,
有时低音不一定是和弦的一部分，
it's an alternate bass we call in the business,
这在业务中称为交替低音，
okay, so you'll see like an F chord slash G,
好的，你会看到 F 和弦斜杠 G ，
well, that's an f chord with A G in the bass,
这是一个 F 和弦使用 G 作为低音，
how I would play that is something like this,
我弹奏它是这样的，
here's my F chord, and then I added the G into the bass,
这是我的 F 和弦，然后我在低音加上 G 。
Okay, and again that diamond is telling you which root that you can use
好的，再次，那个钻石符号告诉你可以使用哪个跟音，
and you can transpose that wherever you want it to.
你可以把它转到你想去的任何地方。
Okay, another one is a D with an E in the bass,
好的，另一个是 D 使用 E 作为低音，
let's do this on the fifth string,
让我们在第五弦上做这件事，
wait a minute, right here,
等一下，在这里，
we have a D triad with an E in the bass,
我们有一个 D 三和弦，使用 E 作为低音，
that would be a D with an E in the bass.
那是 D 使用 E 作为低音。
Here's some inversion chord forms that you may not be familiar with,
这里有一些你可能不熟悉的转位和弦形式，
we already talked about a couple of them,
我们已经谈过其中的几个，
a D with an F# is like this,
D 加上 F# 是这样的，
and E with a G# a little bit of a stretch,
E 加上 G# 有点拉伸，
it was like that,
它是这样的，
and open G with a B is like that,
G 加上 B 是这样的，
what about a C a Bb chord with a C in the bass,
Bb 使用 C 作为低音是怎么样的，
that's pretty easy chord,
这是相当容易的和弦，
one big barre here,
在这里放一个大横按，
or you can play it up here as well.
或者你也可以在这里弹奏。
Okay, now let's talk about some really cool chords,
好的，现在让我们谈谈一些非常酷的和弦，
that you can use and incorporate into your playing,
你可以使用它们并将它们融入你的演奏中，
I don't have any other way to say it,
我没有其他的方法来表达，
but they use the E and the B string
但他们使用 E 和 B 弦，
and they just kind of end up with this cool droning sound,
它们只是以这种很酷的嗡嗡声结束，
so guitar players can come up with these little tricks like this
所以吉他演奏者可以想出这样的小技巧，
and you end up with some very colorful chords without having to think too hard,
你不必费力思考就可以得到一些非常五颜六色的和弦，
and you can use your fingers and patterns to come up with really cool chords,
你可以用你的手指和模式来得到非常酷的和弦，
this would be like an E5,
这是一个 E5 ，
now if I take the same form
现在，如果我采用相同的形式，
and I move it down to let's say C,
我把它下移到 C ，
I end up with a Cmaj7,
我最终得到了 Cmaj7 ，
if I counted all those notes up together,
如果我把所有这些音符加在一起，
okay, if I did it in D,
好的，如果我是在 D 做的，
I end up with a D6/9,
我最后得到的是 D6/9 ，
now that may sound a little complex for you,
现在，这对你来说可能听起来有点复杂，
let me play it for you,
我来弹奏给你听，
let me put a little [], little delay,
让我来加一个[]，小的延迟，
very common little progression that a lot of guitar players use,
非常常见的进程，很多吉他演奏者都会用到，
if I take that similar pattern and run it all the way through,
如果我采用类似的模式，并一直运行它，
I end up with an A2, a Bsus,
我最终得到一个 A2 ，一个 Bsus ，
we already talked about a Cmaj7, D6/9, E5,
我们已经谈过了 Cmaj7 D6/9 E5 ，
the last one would be maybe an F#sus right there,
最后一个可能是 F#sus ，
that one doesn't sound too good.
那个听起来不太好。
Okay, so some of them work better than others.
好的，所以它们中的一些比另一些工作得更好。
Okay, now let's go through these F#m11 based ones,
好的，现在让我们来看看 F#m11 ，
okay, so F#m11 we learned is here,
好的，我们学习的 F#m11 在这里，
okay, if I take this up a couple steps,
如果我把这个往上走几步，
I end up with maybe an E2 with a G# in the bass,
我可能会得到一个 E2 使用 G# 作为低音，
I go up one more,
我再上去一次，
I end up with this really hip Am11 chord,
我最终得到了这个非常时髦的 Am11 和弦，
then we have a, maybe a Bmsus,
然后我们有一个，也许是 Bmsus ，
okay, C doesn't sound too good,
好的， C 听起来不太好听，
so we skip that and go to C#
所以我们跳过它，跳到 C# ，
and then Dm
然后是 Dm ，
and maybe Em,
也许还有 Em ，
so you can get a lot of good mileage out of chords like that.
这样你就可以从和弦上得到很多很好的里程数。
Really gives you playing some character and some depth
给了你一些个性和一些深度，
and you don't need to understand all the theory behind it,
你不需要理解背后的所有理论，
even though I hope you do,
即使我希望你这么做，
you can just use those patterns to come up with some really hip chords.
你可以用这些模式来创造出一些真正时髦的和弦。
Okay, two more forms we haven't touched on yet,
好的，还有两种我们还没有接触到的形式，
that you're gonna see,
你会看到的，
one of them is a diminished chord,
其中一种是减弱和弦，
okay, let me give you the six string form that I use all the time,
好的，让我给你我一直使用的六弦形式，
this would be like a G diminished,
这是 G 减弱和弦，
you got a barre here on this first string,
你在第一弦上有一个横按，
second finger up here, third finger down there,
中指在这里，无名指在这里，
I'm muting that fifth string,
我要把第五弦静音，
okay, if I want a five string version of, a fifth string version of it,
好的，如果我想要五根弦的版本，第五弦的版本，
this would be like A C diminished,
这就是 C 减弱。
okay, inside four strings only,
好的，只有中间四根弦，
if I want the fourth string version of it,
只有我想要第四弦的版本，
E diminished like that
E 减弱和弦是这样的。
Now here's a great thing you can do with diminished chords,
现在这里有一件很棒的事情，你可以用减弱和弦来做，
diminished chords involve the same relationship between the notes,
减弱和弦涉及音符之间的相同关系，
C Eb and Gb and an A or Bbb
C Eb Gb A 或 Bbb ，
are all the same distance from each other,
都是相同的距离，
so it allows you to do some pretty cool things on guitar,
所以它可以让你在吉他上做一些很酷的事情，
if the cord is like a G diminished,
如果和弦是 G 减弱，
I could do something like this,
我可以做这样的事情，
I can just keep building on those,
我可以继续在那些构建，
who can get a lot of good mileage out of your diminished towards using them that way,
可以从你以这种方式获得减弱和弦的大量好处，
you can also substitute them for,
你也可以用它们来替换，
like a dominant seventh with a b9,
替换属七和弦加上 b9 ，
okay, so if I have a C7(b9),
好的，如果我有 C7(b9) ，
I can substitute an E diminished in there,
我可以用 E 减弱来代替，
and that's just another little trick for you,
这只是你的另一个小把戏，
you can grab that if you want to.
如果你想的话可以拿着它。
Augmented chords, okay, involve raising that fifth up,
增强和弦，涉及把第五个向上，
six string version that I use this like here,
我在这里使用的第六弦版本，
fifth string version would be something like this.
第五弦版本是这样的。
Those are just some common forms that we use.
这些只是我们使用的一些常见形式。
Folks come to me all the time
人们总是来找我，
and they think, wow, you know, [] different forms,
他们想，哇，[]不同的形式，
well, I really don't know all that many,
嗯，我真的不知道那么多，
I have what I have shown to you over these last twenty sessions
在过去的二十节课中，
is a good eighty, ninety percent of the chords I'll ever use,
我展示给你们的是我使用的和弦的百分之八九十，
I wish when I was growing up,
我希望在我成长的过程中，
somebody would show it, would have shown me,
有人能告诉我，
here's all the chords that I use in my guitar playing lifetime or the majority of them
这是我一生中在吉他演奏中使用的所有和弦，或者大多数和弦，
and I could grab them.
我可以抓住它们。
So yes, there is a few, but write them down in a notebook,
所以，是的，有几个，但把它们写在笔记本上，
and learn them have underneath your fingers,
掌握它们就在你的手指下，
that's one of the things that's been a constant advantage for me,
这是我一直以来的优势之一，
just knowing a few more chords than the guy sitting next to me.
只是比我旁边的人多知道几个和弦。
Okay, and it doesn't take many before folks think you're a guitar chord genius,
好的，不用多久人们就会认为你是吉他和弦天才，
just you know all that means is,
因为，这意味着，
you know, two more chords than a guy sitting next to you.
比在你旁边的人多两个和弦。
Okay.
好的。
When in doubt,
当你犹豫不决时，
you don't know what the chord is,
你不知道这个和弦是什么，
build it, that's why we've done all this chord spelling exercises.
把它建起来，这就是为什么我们做了这么多和弦拼写练习。
Okay, a chord is just a combination of notes,
好的，和弦只是音符的组合，
all you have to do is get those three or four notes together
你所要做的就是把这三四个音符放在一起，
and you have a chord,
你就有了一个和弦，
or you can also go into your Mel Bay's Guitar Bible big chord dictionary,
或者你也可以进入你的 Mel Bay 吉他圣经，大型和弦词典，
those are mildly helpful,
这些都是有一定帮助的，
a lot of times, it's just the same twenty chords done in in a bunch of different keys
很多时候，同样的 20 个和弦被放在一堆不同的调子里，
and they make a big, real thick book
它们构成了一本很大、很厚的书，
and make you pay a bunch of money for them,
让你花了一大笔钱，
but sometimes if you need a quick chord fast,
但有时，如果你需要一个快速和弦，
you can look it up there,
你可以在那里找到它，
you can always go online and look up chords as well.
你可以随时上网，也可以查找和弦。
Okay, now one more thing I want to talk about in our guitar tip section here is practicing,
好的，现在我想在吉他技巧部分再谈一件事就是练习，
practicing is something you're gonna be doing all of your life,
练习是你一生都要做的事情，
and it's something that we can practice in a smart way,
我们可以用一种聪明的方式练习的东西，
or we can just noodle around and waste a bunch of time,
或者我们可以只是闲逛，浪费一大堆时间，
and never get what we want to get done,
永远做不到我们想做的事，
you always want to practice,
你总是想要练习，
here's some practice keys,
这是一些练习关键，
practice with a purpose in mind,
练习时心中要有目标，
practice, I I play guitar for a living,
练习，我以弹吉他为生，
when I have to practice something,
当我必须练习一些东西时，
I practice it to learn that one particular part,
我会练习它来学习那个特定的部分，
I don't go through the whole song versus choruses,
我不会一口气练完整首歌和合唱，
all that sort of stuff to get to that tricky guitar part,
所有这类东西都是为了达到复杂的吉他部分，
that's not what helps me,
这对我没什么帮助，
I go right to the tricky guitar part that I need to figure out
我直接进入我需要弄清楚的棘手的吉他部分，
and I practice it,
然后练习它，
you go slow,
你慢慢来，
how slow do you need to go,
你需要多慢，
you need to go as slow as you possibly can,
你需要尽可能地慢下来，
to get it right
把它做好，
and then slowly increase your speed,
然后慢慢提高速度，
so the first thing of practicing,
所以练习的第一件事，
is go slow in practice with a purpose.
慢一点，在练习中有目标，
Next thing you want to do is
下一件你想做的事是，
always practice a little bit each day,
每天都练习一点，
guitar playing is not like some other hobbies or crafts,
吉他演奏和其他一些爱好或手艺不同，
it's something that you have to keep up,
这是你必须保持的东西，
there's a lot of physical things that we do
我们有很多身体上的事情，
need to practice a little bit each day,
确实需要每天练习一点，
what's enough,
什么就足够了，
well, I don't know,
我不知道，
if you can spend twenty minutes, five out of seven days of the week with your guitar,
如果你能一周七天中的五天，花二十分钟在你的吉他上，
you're making good progress,
你进步很快，
okay, I hear about these guys that,
我听说这些家伙，
oh yeah, when I was a teenager,
哦，是的，当我还是个十几岁的孩子的时候，
I spent eight, nine hours with my guitar,
我花了八九个小时弹吉他，
well, great, that's fabulous,
好的，那太好了，
for me, if I can grab 15, 20 minutes,
对于我来说，如果我能抽出 15 20 分钟，
I think it's a success,
我认为就是成功的，
so see if you can grab, set aside some time to do that,
所以，看看你是否能抓住机会，
a little bit each day,
每天留出一点时间来做这件事，
and you'll get some good progress done.
你会取得一些好的进展。
Okay.
好的。
There is no substitute for diligent practice,
没有什么可以代替勤奋的练习，
just go after it a little bit,
只要稍微去追求它就好，
is it fun,
它好玩吗，
no, I do it for a living and it's never fun,
不，我是以此为生的，从来都不好玩，
so get over that,
所以忘了这件事吧，
it wasn't fun when I was a kid and it's not fun,
当我还是个孩子的时候，这并不好玩，一点也不好玩，
now, it's something that you have to do,
现在，这是你必须做的事情，
like lifting weights, to get where you want to be is the practicing.
比如举重，到达你想去的地方就是练习。
Okay, let me tell you another secret,
好的，让我告诉你另一个秘密，
it's the power of warming up,
就是热身的力量，
and most musicians, we're in a hurry and we're lazy,
而大多数音乐家，我们很忙，我们很懒，
and we never get around to actually playing a few minutes
我们从来没有抽出时间几分钟演奏，
before we're actually supposed to get up and play,
在我们真正演奏之前，
whether you're playing at church or whether you're playing with friends or something like that,
无论你是在教堂演奏，还是和朋友一起演奏，
it's a good idea to get a few minutes of practicing in before you play,
在演奏之前先练习几分钟都是个好主意，
here's what I do when I warm up,
这是我热身时要做的事情，
I usually go through a major scale,
我通常会做一个大调音阶，
I set my metronome on 60
我把我的节拍器设置在 60 ，
and I just do sixteenth notes through a major major scale,
我只是通过一个大调音阶做十六分音符，
be something like this,
大概是这样的，
then I go to the next form
然后我转到下一个形式，
and I keep going through all of that form,
我继续练习所有的形式，
all the way up the entire neck of the instrument,
一直到乐器的整个琴颈，
and then I go back down again.
然后我再往下走。
Okay, I can get through that as I slowly,
好的，我可以慢慢地通过，
and then I come all the way down,
然后一路往下走，
then I crank my metronome up a click
然后我把我的节拍器向上一点，
and that gets me to like 64,
到达比如 64 ，
and then I do it again,
然后我再做一次，
and usually by about twenty minutes,
通常是大约 20 分钟，
I'm usually around 120 or so, when I'm able to do sixteenth notes at 120,
我通常在 120 ，当我能够在 120 做十六分音符的时候，
now that I've found, I found that,
我发现，
if I don't do the slower steps and I skip those,
如果我不做那些较慢的步骤，而跳过那些步骤，
then I just don't get to where I could have gotten had I taken the time to go through it slow,
那么我就不会达到我花时间慢慢走过的地方，
it's kind of like lifting weights,
这有点像举重，
you don't just walk into the gym and throw up your highest weight
你不能就这样走进健身房，做最高重量，
and expect to bench press it
然后指望用仰卧撑来支撑它，
and you gotta work your way up to it,
然后你必须努力做到这一点，
musicians are athletes of small muscles
音乐家是小肌肉运动员，
and so a lot of what we do is physical,
所以我们做的很多事情都是身体上的，
so a good time warming up is well worth it.
所以一段美好的热身时光是非常值得的。
You can do major scales, you can do panatonic scales,
你可以做大调音阶，你可以做五声音阶，
basically, it's just getting your blood flowing
基本上，这只是让你的血液流动，
and getting your fingers used to firing together.
让你的手指习惯于一起开火。
Okay, you can do a chromatic scale,
好的，你可以做一个半音音阶，
here's a good example of a chromatic scale,
这是一个很好的半音音阶例子，
starting at the fifth fret on this A
从这个第五个品的 A 开始，
and I slide down to the next string,
我滑到下一个弦，
back of fret, next string,
下一品，下一根弦，
back of fret,
下一品，
now here I stay
我停在这里，
and there A again,
又回到 A ，
good finger exercise to get you doing,
很好的手指练习，
remember our finger exercises like this,
记住我们的手指练习，
all these things are good to warm up on.
所有这些东西都是热身的好东西。
Okay, now let me share with you the key to playing fast,
好的，现在让我和你分享一下快速演奏的秘诀，
we'd make a million dollars,
我们会赚一百万美元，
if I could tell you the key to playing fast is in some little trick,
如果我可以告诉你，玩得快的关键在于一些小把戏，
I've been playing all my life,
我这辈子都在弹奏，
here's the only trick I have found to playing fast,
这是我发现的唯一一个快速弹奏的诀窍，
despite all the books and videos that I've gotten,
尽管我已经收到了所有的书籍和视频，
the key to playing fast is slow down,
弹奏快的关键是慢下来，
If I'm trying to play a lick super fast,
如果我想弹奏得超快，
here's two ways I can do it,
我有两种方法可以做到，
if I just start,
如果我开始，
here's what the average person does,
这是普通人会做的事情，
They take the look, let's say I'm gonna do the pentatonic scale,
他们会弹奏比如，我要做的是五声音阶，
and they just play it as fast as they can
他们以最快的速度演奏，
and they do something like that
他们做一些类似的事情，
and they just kind of fake there and fluff their way through it,
他们只是假装在那里，用他们的方式来完成它，
and they think they're playing fast,
他们认为自己弹奏得很快，
okay, that's not real effective,
好的，这并不是很有效，
here's what I found,
这是我发现的，
actually get some improvement in playing fast,
在快速弹奏方面得到了一些改进，
go slow until you can actually play it,
放慢速度，直到你能真正弹它为止，
you're playing every note,
你在弹奏每一个音符，
everything's in control,
一切都在掌控之中，
you do it again,
你再来一次，
you slowly kick up your metronome,
你慢慢地启动你的节拍器，
you slowly do it again,
你慢慢地再一次，
slowly do it again,
慢慢地再一次，
eventually you'll get up high enough to where you're actually playing it fast,
最终，你会快到足够高的高度，达到你弹奏的速度，
but you're in control,
但你是在控制之中，
and that's the key to playing fast,
这是弹奏得快的关键，
What is a way,
什么是一种方法，
a humongous waste of your time as a player is to just keep hitting that wall,
作为一名弹奏者，不断地撞墙是对你时间的巨大浪费，
oh, wait a minute I can do it better,
哦，等一下，我可以做得更好，
wait a minute, and just keep hitting that wall,
等一下，一直撞那堵墙，
if I did five minutes of starting slow,
如果我慢慢开始 5 分钟，
that's worth thirty minutes of me sitting there in my bed, hitting the wall every time
那就比得上我坐在床上 30 分钟，每次都撞到墙上，
and, and trying to do that,
然后努力做到这一点，
I hope that makes some sense to you,
我希望你能明白这一点，
your fingers will only do what you've trained them to do,
你的手指只会做你训练它们做的事，
a wonderful quote by a fantastic guitarist, Chris Proctor, classical guitarist,
一位出色的吉他手，古典吉他手， Chris Proctor ，
as he said,
他说过，
in your head is every musical idea you've ever heard,
在你的脑海中是每个你听过的音乐想法，
but your fingers will only do what they've been trained to do,
但你的手指只会做它们训练过的事情，
and that is so true,
这是真的，
if you want to be able to play those hot licks,
如果你想要弹奏这些激烈的片段，
it's not just gonna come to you in the heat of battle,
你不仅要在激烈的战斗中做到这一点，
you've got to go through and pay your dues
你还必须完成并付出你的努力，
and do all these exercises
并进行所有这些练习，
to get them underneath your fingers,
以使它们掌握在你的手指之下，
okay, that brings me to the last point of
好的，这把我带到了最后一点，
being a good musician in practicing
通过练习成为一名优秀的音乐家，
the power of inspiration and perseverance,
灵感和毅力的力量，
if you're an average player,
如果你是一名普通的演奏者，
you kind of get sick of hearing yourself for a while
你会在一段时间内厌倦倾听自己的声音，
and you go through seasons,
然后经历几个季度，
if I play a little bit better,
如果我弹奏得更好一点，
then I play don't play quite as well
那么我就不会弹奏得那么好，
and I'm not too interested in my playing,
我对自己的演奏不太感兴趣，
if you find yourself in a dry season of playing,
如果你发现自己处在一个演奏枯燥的季节，
you need to get inspired, buddy,
你需要得到灵感，伙计，
go down, buy yourself a CD, go out here some musicians,
去给自己买张 CD ，出去找几个音乐家，
and take an evening and go do that,
花一个晚上的时间去做这件事，
get some inspiration back into your musical mind,
在你的音乐头脑中找回一些灵感，
that will help you,
那会对你有帮助，
go the distance and get some new ideas,
全力以赴，想出一些新点子，
you know I've heard a quote that,
我听过这样一句话，
a fool just keeps doing the same thing over and over
傻瓜总是一遍又一遍地做同样的事情，
and expects different results to happen,
却期待着不同的结果，
if you want new things to happen when you're playing,
如果你想在弹奏的时候发生新的事情，
get some new ideas, new inspiration,
那就得到一些新的想法，新的灵感，
that's one thing get inspired,
这是一回事，获得灵感，
watch some other players figure out what they're doing,
看着其他弹奏家，弄清楚他们在做什么，
go up and ask them,
上去问他们，
what gear are you using,
你们用的是什么装备，
what are you playing there,
你在那里弹奏什么，
the other thing that I found that makes a difference,
我发现的另一件事是不同的，
and this is from someone who's played all of his life,
这来自于一个弹奏了一辈子的人，
is perseverance, You need to keep doing it,
那就是毅力，你需要继续这样做，
you need to keep doing it and work hard at it,
你需要继续这样做，并努力工作，
it's not just gonna come by watching a video series,
这可不是看一部视频就能做到的，
I wish it would,
我也希望是这样，
I'd be a very rich man, if it would,
如果真是这样，我会是个很有钱的人，
but it's not,
但事实并非如此，
it comes by working hard at it,
它是通过努力来实现的，
a lot of these concepts we've given you take a lot of time,
我们给你的这些概念中的很多都需要很长时间，
it's easy for me to explain,
这对我来说很容易解释，
but it takes a lot of time for you to understand,
但你要花很多时间才能理解，
so I just encourage you,
所以我鼓励你，
persevere in it and you'll be able to get to the results that you're acting,
坚持下去，你就能达到你所做的事情的结果，
that you're wanting to get out of your own playing.
你想从你自己的弹奏中获得的。
Okay, here's some last minute keys to being a good musician,
好的，这里有一些成为一名好音乐家最后的关键，
when you're in a band situation,
当你在乐队里的时候，
work to compliment what the other people are doing,
努力赞美别人的表演，
don't just play, don't just copy what they're doing,
不要只是弹奏，不要只是模仿他们在做的事情，
if the piano player playing chords
如果钢琴演奏者演奏和弦，
and you got a keyboard player playing chords,
而键盘演奏者演奏和弦，
the last thing we need you as a as a guitar player is to be chunking out the chords too,
作为吉他演奏者，我们最不需要的就是也弹奏和弦，
that's adding nothing to the band mix,
这并没有给乐队的组合增加任何东西，
if you already have a keyboard player that is doing that,
如果你已经有一个键盘手在做这件事，
you need to think of something interesting,
你需要想点有意思的事情，
that compliments what they're doing,
称赞他们的所作所为，
if they're just chunking off the chords,
如果他们只是在弹奏和弦，
maybe you could do something,
也许你能做点什么，
and again, it doesn't have to be complex,
再说一次，这不一定很复杂，
but you could do something like,
但你可以做一些像这样的事情，
now, [], I have a really hooky little guitar part,
我有一个非常古怪的吉他部分，
I'm not playing anything complex,
我不想弹奏什么复杂的东西，
I'm using a couple of different notes,
我用了几个不同的音符，
so it's not hard,
所以不难，
it's just playing something [hooky],
它只是弹奏一些[]，
and I'm listening to the other musicians around this,
我在听周围的其他音乐家的声音，
that's your big key.
那就是你的关键。
Okay, if everyone is playing high,
好的，如果每个人都弹奏很高，
the last thing they need me doing is up there high with them,
他们最不需要我做的事就是和他们一起在高音，
then it just becomes this big garbled mess,
然后它就变成了一个巨大的乱七八糟的烂摊子，
if they're high, I go low,
如果他们高，我就低，
if they're low, I get I go to the higher [register],
如果他们是低的，我得到我去更高的，
If everybody's playing busy, I simplify and do something like that,
如果每个人都很忙，我就会简化并做一些类似的事情，
if everybody has open spaces, then I might get a little busier,
如果每个人都有开放的空间，那么我可能会变得更忙，
give it a little bit of a beat happening.
让它发生一点节拍。
Okay, those are some secrets to coming up with good guitar parts,
好了，这些是一些秘诀，获得好的吉他[]，
that separates you from other players,
将你和其他弹奏者区分开，
get out of your own playing,
从你自己的弹奏中走出来，
don't just think when you're in a band situation,
不要只想，当你在乐队的时候，
it's all about me
这一切都是关于我的，
and I'm so all concerned about these chords that I'm doing and stuff like that,
我非常关心我正在做的这些和弦之类的事情，
listen to what's going on around you,
听听你周围发生了什么，
that's what's going to make
这就是要做的事情，
give you the creative ideas to be able to make some good music
给你创造性的想法，让你能够制作一些好的音乐，
and remember the purpose and you're playing,
记住你演奏的目的，
you want to play with a purpose,
你想要带着一个目的去弹奏，
I don't wanna just play just for fun,
我不想只是为了好玩而弹奏，
even though it is a blast to play,
尽管这是一件令人兴奋的事情，
but play to get enjoyment out of your life
但我想弹奏是为了从你的生活中获得乐趣，
and also to enrich the lives of others.
也为了丰富别人的生活。
Okay, here's your assignment for this week,
好的，这是你们这周的作业，
I want you to practice the alternate base chords and the chord progressions
我要你们练习交替低音和弦和和弦进程，
that we have in the back of your book,
我们在书后面的，
okay, those chord exercises are real helpful,
好的，这些和弦练习是很有帮助的，
and you can get a lot of good working out of these chord forms underneath your fingers,
你可以在手指下的这些和弦形式中得到很多很好的锻炼，
if you do them,
如果你这么做的话，
the idea is to be able to get them fast,
我们的想法是能够快速地获得它们，
where you can grab them immediately,
你可以立即抓住它们，
that's where you're gonna get some good mileage out of these chords,
这就是你会从这些和弦得到一些好处的地方，
practice the open E\B kind of droning chords, like this,
练习开放 E/B 和弦，就像这样，
play around with this very common sound,
用这个非常常见的声音演奏，
these days everybody's using it,
如今，每个人都在使用它，
mess around with it,
把它弄乱，
see if you can come up with some own progressions of your own,
看看你是否能想出一些你自己的进程，
that can lead you into some creative territory.
把你带到一些创造性的领域。
I also want you to learn these new chord forms,
我还想让你们学习这些新的和弦形式，
we talked about diminished, augmented,
我们谈到了减弱，增强，
get a few of those underneath your fingers,
让一些在你的手指下，
I don't know a ton of augmented or diminished chords,
我不知道有多少增强或减弱的和弦，
I know one on each string,
我知道在每个弦上都有，
I know three, yet,
我知道有三个，
you can, you'll be amazed how much you can impress people,
你会惊讶地发现，你会给人们留下多么深刻的印象，
if you just know a couple of chords like that.
如果你只知道几个这样的和弦。
It's been an honor and a privilege being able to teach you,
能够教给你们是一种荣誉，
and I hope that some of the concepts and ideas that I have been able to share,
我希望我能够分享的一些概念和想法，
really sink down deep into your playing
真正沉浸在你的演奏中，
and will change the way you play for the rest of your life,
并将在你的余生中改变你的演奏方式，
we'll see you.
我们会再见到你的。
Okay, welcome to the workshop,
好的，欢迎来到 workshop ，
we covered an awful lot of ground with our various chord forms that we learned,
我们用我们所学的各种和弦形式覆盖了非常多的领域，
the alternate bass chord forms,
交替的低音和弦形式，
let's just review a couple of those,
让我们来回顾一下其中的几个，
what is a D with an F# in the bass,
D 使用 F# 作为低音是什么样的，
remember that, slash is telling you the note underneath the slash is what note is in the bass,
记住，斜杠告诉你，斜杠下面的音符是低音中的音符，
it's not two chords you're playing,
它不是你演奏的两个和弦，
it's one chord with a certain note in the bass,
这是一个和弦，在低音上有一个特定的音符，
so a D with an F# in the bass,
所以 D 在低音上有一个 F# ，
remember that chord form,
记住那个和弦形式，
what about an E with a G# in the bass,
E 使用 G# 作为低音是什么样的，
what about a B, or excuse me, a G chord with a B in the bass.
B 怎么样，抱歉， G 和弦使用 B 作为低音。
Okay, so let's do a little chord progression,
好的，让我们来做一点和弦进程，
let's say, let's do a G to a D with an F# in the bass
比如，从 G 到 D\F# ，
to maybe an Em7, to a Dsus,
到 Em7 ，到 Dsus ，
okay, so let be something like this,
好的，就像这样，
one two, G, go,
1 2 ， G ，开始，
D with an F# in the bass, Em, Dsus,
D/F# Em Dsus ，
one more time, G, D with an F# in the,
再来一次， G D/F# Em Dsus ，
maybe we could go to a C, maybe C2, G with B in the bass,
也许我们可以到 C ， C2 ， G/B ，
C2, G with the B in the bass,
C2 G/B ，
Dsus, maybe a D, D with F#, G.
Dsus D D/F# G 。
Great, see how all those chords work together,
好的，看看这些和弦是如何协同工作的，
let's cover a couple of more,
让我们再来介绍几个，
remember our diminished forms that we talked about,
记得我们所谈到的减弱形式，
how do you do a diminished form on the sixth string on,
你如何在第六弦上做一个减弱形式，
let's say a Bb,
比如在 Bb 上，
What if you saw Bb diminished, where would you go,
如果你看到 Bb 减弱，你应该到哪里，
well, here's the form
好的，这是形式，
and I just here's my root, I go up to Bb
这是我的根音，我走到 Bb 的地方，
and there's my Bb diminished,
这是我的 Bb 减弱和弦，
what if I wanted it on the fifth string form,
如果我想要它在第五弦形式上，
and I wanted an E diminished,
我想要 E 减弱和弦，
well, no problem, that be here,
没问题，它在这里，
fourth string here,
四弦在这里，
six string here,
六弦在这里，
remember repeats every step and a half,
记得，它会重复每一步半，
so this is an E diminished,
所以这是一个 E 减弱和弦，
this is an E diminished,
这是一个 E 减弱和弦，
they're all E diminished,
它们都是 E 减弱和弦，
because all of the scale tones very conveniently,
因为所有的音阶音调都非常方便，
or all the same distance from each other,
彼此之间的距离都是一样的，
so we can move them around.
所以我们可以移动它们。
Augmented chords. Let's cover a couple of those,
增强和弦，让我们来介绍一下其中的几个，
remember our F augmented that we touched on,
记得我们的 F 增强和弦，
okay, remember our C augmented,
好的，记得我们的 C 增强和弦吗，
okay, let's do a little exercise,
好的，让我们做点练习，
let's do like a Cm9,
我们来做 Cm9 ，
to maybe an Fm, to a G augmented,
到可能是 Fm ，到 G+7 ，
okay, one, two, Cm9, go,
好的，1 2 ， Cm9 ，开始，
Fm7, G+7.
Fm7 ， G+7 。
Great, okay, now adding these chords to your chord vocabulary
好的，将这些和弦添加到你的和弦词汇中，
will help you go a long way into,
将帮助你进入很长一段，
just being creative in what you wanna do,
在你想做的事情上有创意，
it's been a wonderful series,
这是一个很棒的系列，
that we've been able to go through,
我们能够度过，
I would encourage you to keep up this good work
我鼓励你们继续保持这一良好的工作，
and always strive to keep hitting the high notes
始终努力保持高音，
and keep striving for new things.
不断争取新的东西。
We'll see you.
我们会再见到你的。